Are you a, a real robot builder?
Well, uh, technically, ah... nah.
Have you ever capped a cap ball, like, uh, like a real expert team?
Nah.
Have you ever tried programming in Java?
Nah, nah...
Alright! I can see that I will have to teach you how to be robot builders!
Hey!
We are number one, hey!
We are number one
Now listen closely
Here's a little lesson in strategy
This is going down is history
If you wanna be alliance number one
You have to chase a cap ball on the run
Just follow my lead, and drive around
Be careful not to pull a wire
No! Don't touch that
We are number one, hey!
We are number one
Hey!
Now look at this ball that I just got
When I say go, be ready to launch
And go!
Throw it in red, not blue!
Uh, let's try something else
Now watch and learn, here's the deal
You turn these beacons from blue to red
What are you doing?!?
Hey!
We are number one, hey!
Robot number one!
Hey!
We are number one, hey!
We are number one, we are number one
We are number one, hey hey!